San Francisco, CA jaimedybuncio@gmail.com (818) 618-4562

Jaime DyBuncio

linkedin.com/in/jaime-dybuncio -94215a20 github.com/jdybuncio

Professional Overview

Data Scientist with six years of experience on the revenue side of technology companies. The primary way I have added value is through building source of truth reporting, which has allowed me to uncover insights, which has then led to me playing critical roles in cross-functional decision making and strategy development.

SKILLS

Core Competencies: SQL, Tableau, Salesforce, Excel Modeling, and building workflows using Treasure Data **Python Programming**: NumPy, Pandas, Scikit-Learn

Data Science: Bootstrapping, Hypothesis Testing, Statistical Modeling, A/B Testing

Machine Learning: Linear/Logistic Regression, Random Forests, Boosting

Experience

Director of Business Operations - Fivestars Loyalty

Mar 2016-Dec 2019

- Created the core data model for all revenue-facing teams which served as the basis of our official numbers. Extracted raw data from Salesforce, Postgres database, and CSVs using Treasure Data.
 Queried using SQL to create data tables allowing creation of business facing dashboards in Tableau.
- Developed and managed in-house commission system which paid out over \$200k per month across 100+ sales and account management reps and their managers. Passed audit every year.
- Built the board-facing monthly recurring revenue model. Introduced a bottom's up model in Excel
 which projected top-line monthly net new MRR projections based on projected headcount, marketing
 lead, sales funnel, and churn performance.
- Presented in front of the board, in-person, after a successful transition of over 50 account management and sales support roles to a centralized El Paso Office in 2018.
- Other roles held at Fivestars: Sales Analyst, Sr. Sales Analyst, and Business Operations Manager.

Senior Marketing Data Analyst - Credit Sesame

2015-2016

- Led strategy shift from acquiring customers at the lowest cost to optimizing ROI which led to a 100% improvement in our LTV:CPA ratio when comparing July to December 2015's customer cohorts.
- Generated customer cohort tracking by Marketing Channel which allowed us to direct \$1mm monthly marketing budget towards best ROI channels.

Sales Operations Associate - Red Ventures

2013-2014

Managed end-to-end sales commissions process for teams over 100 sales reps.

Education

Galvanize San Francisco, CA Data Science Immersive Bootcamp

2020

 700+ hour data science immersive training program covering core data science areas including probability and statistics, supervised and unsupervised machine learning algorithms, and NLP.

Davidson College - B.A., Economics Honor Graduate, Magna Cum Laude, Phi Beta Kappa

2009-2013